Guide to the Yale College, Records of the Yale Bands
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1901-2013; Accession 2015-A-063
  - Audiovisual material
    - Yale Concert Band (YCB)
      - Glenn Miller Band, Eyewitness News, 1995 May 28; 1 (Box 143)
      - 1995 October 26, 1 (Box 144)
      - 1995 December 1, 1 (Box 145)
        Recording is minus Granger's Children's March due to technical problems.
      - Sounds of the Silver Screen, 1996 February; 1 (Box 146)
      - Guest conductors: Jerry Sierra, Delvin Case, 1996 April 12; 1 (Box 147)
      - D-Day, the Whole Story, 1996 June; 1 (Box 148)
      - Winter Concert, 1996 December 15; 1 (Box 149)
      - Has "Cave of the Winds", 1997 February 14; 1 (Box 150)
      - Ireland tour, tape #1, 1997 March; 1 (Box 151)
      - Ireland tour, tape #2, 1997 March; 1 (Box 152)
      - With Penn Wind Ensemble, 1997 April 12; 1 (Box 153)
      - 1997 October 17, 1 (Box 154)
      - 1997 December 3, 1 (Box 155)
      - Four Score and Seven Years Ago, Richard Broadhead, narrator, 1998 February 12; 1 (Box 156)
      - Blue Ink II, 1998 April; 1 (Box 157)
      - Rhapsody in Blue with Dean Blocker, 1998 October 26; 1 (Box 158)
      - Robert van Sice, 1998 November 18; 1 (Box 159)
      - With Ransom Wilson, flute, 1999 February 12; 1 (Box 160)
      - Violas and Verse, Woolsey Hall, 1999 April 9; 1 (Box 161)
      - Music of the Movies, 1999 October 15; 1 (Box 162)
      - Glenn Miller Show, 2000 February 11; 1 (Box 163)
      - CBDNA: Music of Charles Ives with James Sinclair, conductor, 2000 March 31; 1 (Box 164)
      - Firebird, 2000 April 14; 1 (Box 165)
      - YCB 2000, 2000 October 13; 1 (Box 166)
      - YCB Remembers Cole Porter: An American Icon short demo, 2002 February
      - American Classics, 2001 February 9; 1 (Box 167)
      - "Ask the Sky and the Earth: A Cantata for the Sent-Down Youth", 2001 February 11
      - Yale Concert Band Remembers Cole Porter: An American Icon, 2002 February 15
      - Music for Prague 1968 at Woolsey Hall, 2001 March 30; 1 (Box 168)
      - Duffy, "Three Places in New Haven," R. van Sice, marimba, 2001 October 12; 1 (Box 169)
      - YCB 2001, 2001 November 14; 1 (Box 170)
      - Thomas Duffy, "Star Wars", 2002 April 5; 1 (Box 171)
      - Cole Porter, an American Icon, 2002 June 7; 1 (Box 172)
      - Cole Porter, an American Icon, 2002 June 7; 1 (Box 173)
      - Frosh Preview, 2002 October 11; 1 (Box 343)
      - Parents' Weekend, 2002 October 12; 1 (Box 344)
      - Russian and Godfrey piano concerts, 2003 February 21; 1 (Box 345)
      - Children's concert, tape 1, 2003 April 6; 1 (Box 346)
      - Children's concert, tape 2, 2003 April 6; 1 (Box 347)
      - At Shostakovich Hall, St. Petersburg, Russia, 2003 June 4; 1 (Box 174)
      - 2003 October 10, 1 (Box 348)
      - "Corpus Callosum", T.C.D. in costume, 2003 November 6; 1 (Box 349)
      - 2003 December 5, 1 (Box 350)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2004 February 20; 1 (Box 351)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2004 February 20; 1 (Box 352)
      - 2004 April 16, 1 (Box 353)
      - Rehearsals, 2004 September; 1 (Box 354)
      - 2004 October 14, 1 (Box 355)
      - Glenn Miller, 2004 November; 1 (Box 356)
      - 2005 April 8, 1 (Box 357)
      - Rehearsals 1 and 2, 2005 fall; 1 (Box 358)
      - Go Away, 2005 fall; 1 (Box 359)
      - 2006 February 17, 1 (Box 360)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2006 October 13; 1 (Box 361)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2006 October 13; 1 (Box 362)
      - Yale Concert Band: A Sampler DVD, 2006 December
      - Woolsey Hall, tape 1 of 2, 2006 December 1; 1 (Box 363)
      - Woolsey Hall, tape 2 of 2, 2006 December 1; 1 (Box 364)
      - "Cave of Winds" concert, 1 of 2, 2007 February 23; 1 (Box 365)
      - "Cave of Winds" concert, 2 of 2, 2007 February 23; 1 (Box 366)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2007 April 13; 1 (Box 367)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2007 April 13; 1 (Box 368)
      - 2007 October 4, 1 (Box 369)
      - 2007 November 30, 1 (Box 370)
      - 2007 November 30, 1 (Box 371)
      - Rehearsal, 2008; 1 (Box 372)
      - United States Coast Guard Band, Woolsey, 2008 February 15; 1 (Box 373)
      - United States Coast Guard Band, Woolsey, 2008 February 15; 1 (Box 374)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2008 April 4; 1 (Box 375)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2008 April 4; 1 (Box 376)
      - Moving camera, 2008 October 10; 1 (Box 377)
      - Fixed camera, stage right, 1 of 2, 2008 October 10; 1 (Box 378)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2008 October 10; 1 (Box 379)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2008 November 19; 1 (Box 380)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2008 November 19; 1 (Box 381)
      - 2009 February 13, 1 (Box 382)
      - ¡Vamos a Mexico!, 2009 February 13; 1 (Box 383)
      - 2009 April 3, 1 (Box 384)
      - 2009 April 3, 1 (Box 385)
      - Part 1 of 2, 2009 April 3; 1 (Box 386)
      - Part 2, 2009 April 3; 1 (Box 387)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2009 October 9; 1 (Box 388)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2009 October 9; 1 (Box 389)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2009 December 4; 1 (Box 390)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2009 December 4; 1 (Box 391)
      - Glenn Miller sound effects for radio play, 2010
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2010 February 19; 1 (Box 392)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2010 February 19; 1 (Box 393)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2010 April 9; 1 (Box 394)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2010 April 9; 1 (Box 395)
      - Yale Concert Band: A Sampler DVD, 2010 April 9
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2010 October 8; 1 (Box 396)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2010 October 8; 1 (Box 397)
      - "Projections: Pictures at an Exhibition", 2010 October 8
      - Cole Porter and Glenn Miller Return to New Haven, tape 1, 2010 December 3; 1 (Box 398)
      - Cole Porter and Glenn Miller Return to New Haven, tape 2, 2010 December 3; 1 (Box 399)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2011 April 15; 1 (Box 400)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2011 April 15; 1 (Box 401)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2011 October 14; 1 (Box 402)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2011 October 14; 1 (Box 403)
      - At Woolsey, 2011 December 2; 1 (Box 404)
      - "Silver Screen", 2012 February 10; 1 (Box 405)
        Master, incomplete: missing Halo, Parliament, Faust I-III (recording error).
      - "The Silver Screen", 2012 February 10
      - Miller, tape #1: Testimony, Park Plaza, [No Year] February 26; 1 (Box 175)
      - #2 Prior, Trinity College, Lawrence, Undated; 1 (Box 176)
      - D-Day and 40 Years, Undated; 1 (Box 177)
      - Glenn Miller Remembered, Undated; 1 (Box 178)
      - Miburi/Hiroshi, Undated; 1 (Box 179)
      - Rehearsal, with student conductor, Undated; 1 (Box 320)
      - Background on Glenn Miller tour and concert; audio only discussion of general quality of performers and performances in concert band and symphony orchestra, Undated; 1 (Box 321)
      - Santos concert 1, Undated; 1 (Box 409)
      - Santos 2, Sorocaba 1, Undated; 1 (Box 410)
      - 1. Santos, Brazil, Undated
      - Sorocaba 2, Undated; 1 (Box 417)
      - 2. Sorocaba, Brazil, Undated
      - Fun in Campinas, Undated; 1 (Box 408)
      - Campinas 1, Undated; 1 (Box 406)
      - Campinos 2, São Paulo 1, Undated; 1 (Box 418)
      - 3. Campinas, Brazil, Undated
      - São Paulo 2, Undated; 1 (Box 412)
      - Free time - São Paulo, Santos, Undated; 1 (Box 413)
      - 4. São Paulo, Brazil, Undated
      - Rio 1, first tape, Undated; 1 (Box 407)
      - Rio 1, second tape, Undated; 1 (Box 416)
      - Rio fun 1, Undated; 1 (Box 411)
      - Rio second, first tape, Undated; 1 (Box 414)
      - Rio concert 2, second tape, Undated; 1 (Box 415)
      - 5. Rio de Janiero (1), Undated
      - 6. Rio de Janiero (2), Undated
      - Mexico City, Undated; 1 (Box 419)
      - Monterrey, Undated; 1 (Box 420)
      - San Miguel, Undated; 1 (Box 421)
      - "Parliament," by A.A. Roberts, Undated
      - Cole Porter 1, Undated
      - Star Wars, Undated
    - Yale Jazz Ensemble (YJE)
      - 1st Jazz Festival with Mel Lewis and Dick Oates, 1987; 1 (Box 180)
      - 1st Jazz Festival with Mel Lewis and Dick Oates, 1987; 1 (Box 181)
      - Cole Porter Festival at Norfolk, 1990 September 15; 1 (Box 182)
      - Branford Marsalis, 1990 November 15; 1 (Box 183)
      - Evidence - Ken Todd, 1991 November 13; 1 (Box 184)
      - Jimmy Owens, 1992 February 19; 1 (Box 185)
      - Goodmania, 1992 April 15; 1 (Box 186)
      - 1993 November 7, 1 (Box 187)
      - 1994 spring, 1 (Box 188)
      - 1994 November 6, 1 (Box 189)
      - A Little Big Band, 1995 March 2; 1 (Box 190)
      - Concert, 1999 November 12; 1 (Box 191)
      - Remembering Mingus, 2000 March 1; 1 (Box 192)
      - Such Sweet Thunder, Sprague Hall, D. Brandenburg, conductor, 2001 February 28; 1 (Box 193)
      - West Side Story March 6, 1992, D. Brandenburg, Director (copy 1), 2002; 1 (Box 194)
      - West Side Story, D. Brandenburg, conductor, 2002 March 6; 1 (Box 195)
      - 2003 March 1, 1 (Box 422)
      - David Brandenburg, Musical Director, Sprague Hall, 2003 November 12; 1 (Box 423)
      - 2004 March 3, 1 (Box 424)
      - 2004 November 17, 1 (Box 425)
      - 2004 November 17, 1 (Box 426)
      - Master, 2005 March 3; 1 (Box 427)
      - Tape 2, 2005 March 3; 1 (Box 428)
      - Tape 1, 2005 November; 1 (Box 429)
      - Tape 2, 2005 November; 1 (Box 430)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2006 February 28; 1 (Box 431)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2006 February 28; 1 (Box 432)
      - 2006 November 15, 1 (Box 433)
      - Battell, 2007 April 15; 1 (Box 434)
      - 2007 November 14, 1 (Box 435)
      - 2008 March 3, 1 (Box 436)
      - A Jazz Tribute to Stan Wheeler, Yale Law School, 2008 April 13
      - Tape 1, 2008 October 17; 1 (Box 437)
      - Tape 2, 2008 October 17; 1 (Box 438)
      - "Nutcracker Swings", 2008 December 4; 1 (Box 439)
      - Sprague Hall, 2009 February 19; 1 (Box 440)
      - Second set, 2009 February 19; 1 (Box 441)
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2009 April 16; 1 (Box 442)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2009 April 16; 1 (Box 443)
      - Stan Wheeler Jazz Concert, Yale Law School, 2009 April 19
      - Tape 1 of 2, 2009 November 9; 1 (Box 444)
      - Tape 2 of 2, 2009 November 9; 1 (Box 445)
      - 2010 February 10, 1 (Box 446)
      - Stan Wheeler Jazz Concert, Yale Law School, 2010 April 16
      - Sprague, tape 1 of 2, 2010 October 15; 1 (Box 447)
      - Sprague, tape 2 of 2, 2010 October 15; 1 (Box 448)
      - Stan Wheeler Jazz Concert, Yale Law School, 2011 April 3
      - 2011 October 10, 1 (Box 449)
      - "Homegrown", 2012 February 29; 1 (Box 450)
      - Stan Wheeler Jazz Concert, Yale Law School, 2012 April 15
      - [No year] March 8, 1 (Box 451)
    - Yale Precision Marching Band (YPMB)
      - Halftime Shows, 1982; 1 (Box 196)
      - Halftimes: Brown, UConn, Morgan State, Dartmouth, Columbia, 1984; 1 (Box 197)
      - Halftimes: Princeton, Harvard, 1984; 1 (Box 198)
      - Movie, "Never Say Her Majesty's Man with the Golden Octopussy and Let Die", 1984; 1 (Box 199)
      - Movie 1984 (copy 1), 1 (Box 200)
      - YPMB's Greatest Hits, 1984; 1 (Box 201)
      - Halftimes: Brown, Army, 1985; 1 (Box 202)
      - Halftimes: Holy Cross, Penn, 1985; 1 (Box 203)
      - Movie, "Stop Making Movies!", 1985; 1 (Box 204)
      - Halftimes: Brown, UConn, Army, Columbia, Colgate, Dartmouth, 1986; 1 (Box 205)
      - Halftimes: Princeton, 1986; 1 (Box 206)
      - Halftimes, Harvard, 1986; 1 (Box 207)
      - Movie, "Chariots of Squid" (copy 1), 1986; 1 (Box 208)
      - Halftimes, Brown, UConn, William and Mary, Penn, 1987; 1 (Box 209)
      - Halftimes: Dartmouth, Cornell, Princeton, 1987; 1 (Box 210)
      - Halftimes, Harvard, 1987; 1 (Box 211)
      - Movie, "Band", 1987; 1 (Box 212)
      - Crashing Harvard's Orientation, 1988; 1 (Box 213)
      - MTV Halloween Parade, 1988; 1 (Box 214)
      - Halftime: Harvard, 1988; 1 (Box 215)
      - Movies, 1988-1989; 1 (Box 216)
      - Halftime, 1989; 1 (Box 217)
      - Halftime: Harvard, 1989; 1 (Box 218)
      - Movie, "Sam - Beardless Duffy", 1989; 1 (Box 219)
      - Movie, "The Fish That Escaped", 1989; 1 (Box 220)
      - Halftimes, 1990; 1 (Box 221)
      - Halftimes: Lafayette, UConn, 1990; 1 (Box 222)
      - No Dorks Allowed (final master), 1990; 1 (Box 223)
      - Halftimes: All but Harvard, 1991; 1 (Box 224)
      - Halftimes: Harvard Explodes, 1991; 1 (Box 225)
      - Movie, 1991; 1 (Box 226)
      - "On the Air" - ABC, Channel 8, 1991 September 6; 1 (Box 227)
      - At Stonehenge, London, 1991 December; 1 (Box 228)
      - At the Barbicon, in London, 1991 December 31; 1 (Box 229)
      - Winter Wonder Band, 1992; 1 (Box 230)
      - Halftimes: Penn, Glee Club, 1993; 1 (Box 231)
      - Halftimes: The Game, 1993; 1 (Box 232)
      - Halftimes: Brown, UConn, Bucknell, Columbia, Cornell, Princeton, 1993; 1 (Box 233)
      - Movie, "Stuffalupagus and Achovies: A Retrospective", 1993; 1 (Box 234)
      - Dartmouth and Jello, 1993; 1 (Box 235)
      - Halftime: Harvard, 1993; 1 (Box 236)
      - Halftime: The Game, 1994; 1 (Box 237)
      - Movie, 1994; 1 (Box 238)
      - Halftimes: UPenn '94 and Columbia '98, 1994 October 29, 1998 October 24; 1 (Box 239)
      - Halftimes: Brown, New Haven 101, 1995; 1 (Box 240)
      - Movie, "Spraying in Asia: Are We Sure?", 1995; 1 (Box 241)
      - Halftime: Princeton, 1995; 1 (Box 242)
      - YPMB, 1995; 1 (Box 243)
      - Hahvahd '95 and Hockey '96 (Harvard 1995; weird guy at b-ball '96; hockey '96), 1995-1996; 1 (Box 244)
      - Halftimes: Brown, UConn, Bucknell, Columbia, Cornell, Princeton, 1996; 1 (Box 245)
      - Halftime: Harvard, 1996; 1 (Box 246)
      - Movie, "…So To Speak", 1996; 1 (Box 247)
      - Random footage, 1996-1997; 1 (Box 248)
      - Random footage, 1996-1997; 1 (Box 249)
      - Halftimes: All Shows, 1997; 1 (Box 250)
      - Movie, "Life of Brian…..Boitano!", 1997; 1 (Box 251)
      - The Big Fat Trip o' Fun in Chicago, 1997 October; 1 (Box 252)
      - Lake Placid, Michigan, also Presidential footage, 1997-1998; 1 (Box 253)
      - Halftimes: Brown, Colgate, Holy Cross, 1998; 1 (Box 254)
      - Halftimes: Cornell, Princeton, 1998; 1 (Box 255)
      - Halftime & Hockey, Harvard football & hockey, 1998; 1 (Box 256)
      - Movie "Go Now!", 1998; 1 (Box 257)
      - Vermont Hockey, 1998; 1 (Box 258)
      - Hockey: Harvard, 1998 February 14; 1 (Box 259)
      - Year in Review 1998-1999 and 1989 Halftime Shows Year in Review 1998-1999 and Halftime Shows with UConn, 1 (Box 260)
      - Halftime: At Brown, 1999; 1 (Box 261)
      - Halftimes: Valpanso, 9/25; Dartmouth, 10/15; Colgate, 12/3; Jell-O Tang (sort of), 1999; 1 (Box 262)
      - Nuking the (Princeton) Tigers, 11/13; Eating the Geeks, 11/14, 1999; 1 (Box 263)
      - Movie, "I Want My Ham!", 1999; 1 (Box 264)
      - Yale hockey game, 1999 January 29; 1 (Box 265)
      - Movie, "Sit Down. D Minus", 2000; 1 (Box 266)
      - Halftime: Harvard, 2000 November 18; 1 (Box 267)
      - "NCAA Football - The Slant", show #414, 2000 December 5; 1 (Box 268)
      - Halftime: United We Stand, 2001; 1 (Box 269)
      - Halftime: United We Stand (copy 1), 2001; 1 (Box 270)
      - Halftime: United We Stand, 2001; 1 (Box 271)
      - Year in Review, 2001; 1 (Box 272)
      - The Year in Review (copy 1), 2001; 1 (Box 273)
      - Movie, "Thwap!", 2001; 1 (Box 274)
      - Stuff and hockey, 2001; 1 (Box 275)
      - Movie, "Lord of the Whistle", 2002; 1 (Box 276)
      - Movies '81, '82, '83 plus Glenn publicity, acquired by Matt B, 2002; 1 (Box 277)
      - YPMB plays Bulldog (in stands), vs. Towson, 2003 September 20; 1 (Box 452)
      - Dartmouth, 2003 October 11; 1 (Box 453)
      - YPMB plays Bulldog (in Y formation), vs. Dartmouth; Band movie plot, 2003 October 11; 1 (Box 454)
      - Year in Review (YIR) final, 2003-2004; 1 (Box 455)
      - Movie (Madness), 2004
      - Movie, "Surewood" - Karl Gunderson, 1 of 2, 2004; 1 (Box 456)
      - Movie, "Surewood" - Karl Gunderson, 2 of 2, 2004; 1 (Box 457)
      - Penn, 2004; 1 (Box 458)
      - Columbia, 2004; 1 (Box 459)
      - CBS Sunday Morning: "Cole Porter", 2004 July 4; 1 (Box 278)
      - The Game, tape 1, 2005; 1 (Box 460)
      - Harvard, tape 2, 2005; 1 (Box 461)
      - Doesn't matter, 2005; 1 (Box 462)
      - 'Neath the Elms, director's cut, 2005 July 30; 1 (Box 279)
      - Dartmouth, 2005 fall; 1 (Box 463)
      - Ben's tongue!, 2005 fall; 1 (Box 464)
      - Aerial dance shots, end of drug scenes, 2006; 1 (Box 465)
      - Film, violence, 2006; 1 (Box 466)
      - Dartmouth, 2006; 1 (Box 467)
      - Princeton vs. Yale, 2006; 1 (Box 468)
      - Script, The Game, 2006; 1 (Box 469)
      - Yale vs. San Diego, 2006 fall; 1 (Box 470)
      - Basketball at Penn, 2006 February; 1 (Box 471)
      - Basketball; doesn't matter, 2006 March 4; 1 (Box 472)
      - Cavalcade '07, 2007; 1 (Box 280)
      - Uberprop!, 2007; 1 (Box 473)
      - Doesn't matter, 2007; 1 (Box 474)
      - Hockey, basketball, Philadelphia, 2007; 1 (Box 475)
      - Hockey, 2007; 1 (Box 476)
      - Cornell game, 2007 September 22; 1 (Box 477)
      - Cornell football, 2007 September 23-24; 1 (Box 478)
      - Dartmouth game, 2007 October 6; 1 (Box 479)
      - Lehigh game at Yale, 2007 October 13; 1 (Box 480)
      - Penn, 2007 October 20; 1 (Box 481)
      - The Game, 2007 November; 1 (Box 482)
      - Brown, 2007 November 3; 1 (Box 483)
      - Uberpropping, 2008; 1 (Box 484)
      - Georgetown halftime, 2008
      - Yale vs. Holy Cross, 2008; 1 (Box 485)
      - Yale vs. Penn, 2008; 1 (Box 486)
      - Yale vs. Columbia, 2008; 1 (Box 487)
      - YPMB Year in Review, 2008
      - Basketball, 2008 January 26; 1 (Box 488)
      - Yale vs. Georgetown, 2008 September 20; 1 (Box 489)
      - The Game, 2008 November; 1 (Box 490)
      - The Game, 2008 November; 1 (Box 491)
      - Yale vs. Princeton, 2008 November 15; 1 (Box 492)
      - DTF, 2009; 1 (Box 493)
      - Random YPMB, 2009; 1 (Box 494)
      - Cornell, Penn, Brown (field rehearsal only), 2009 September 26-November 7; 1 (Box 495)
      - Fayette, Dartmouth, 2009 October 3-10; 1 (Box 496)
      - The Game, 2009 November; 1 (Box 497)
      - Brown, Cornell hockey, Princeton, YPMB vs. Glee Club touch football, 2009 November 7-15; 1 (Box 498)
      - Hockey playoffs, 2009 winter; 1 (Box 499)
      - Hockey playoffs, 2009 winter; 1 (Box 500)
      - Hockey playoffs: second round and Albany, 2009 winter; 1 (Box 501)
      - YPMB sophomore sketch, dead week, 2010; 1 (Box 502)
      - Hockey and football, 2010; 1 (Box 503)
      - YPMB v. Albany, 2010 October 2; 1 (Box 504)
      - YPMB v. Fordham, 2010 October 16; 1 (Box 505)
      - YPMB Year in Review, 2011
      - "Episode MMXII: It's a Trap!", 2011
      - YPMB v. Georgetown, 2011 September 17; 1 (Box 506)
      - YPMB v. Cornell, 2011 September 24; 1 (Box 507)
      - YPMB vs. Dartmouth, 2011 October 8; 1 (Box 508)
      - YPMB at Penn, 2011 October 22; 1 (Box 509)
      - The Game, 2011 November; 1 (Box 510)
      - YPMB at Princeton, 2011 November 12; 1 (Box 511)
      - Movie, tape 1, 2012; 1 (Box 512)
      - Movie, tape 2, 2012; 1 (Box 513)
      - Movie, tape 3, 2012; 1 (Box 514)
      - Cornell, [no year] September 23-24; 1 (Box 515)
      - YPMB Takes Manhattan, Undated; 1 (Box 281)
      - Berman -- Jeopardy, Undated; 1 (Box 282)
      - Mark Tamaris - Jeopardy, Undated; 1 (Box 283)
      - Movie, "I Came…", Undated; 1 (Box 284)
      - "Ryder's Master" (Final cut of YPMB running around to Circle of Life), Undated; 1 (Box 285)
      - Year in Review, Undated; 1 (Box 286)
      - "I Want My Ham!!" final copy and blocked tape, Undated; 1 (Box 287)
      - Black Tape, reduced hits clip, out takes, Undated; 1 (Box 288)
      - The Game, Undated; 1 (Box 318)
      - Movie, scattered scenes, Undated; 1 (Box 319)
      - Basketball and hockey, Undated; 1 (Box 516)
      - S.E.X. movie, Undated; 1 (Box 517)
      - Go Away; Penn; An Diego; Columbia; Penn halftime; The Game, Undated; 1 (Box 518)
      - "InDiana Jones and the Book of Life", Undated
      - "YPMB for Vendetta", Undated
      - YPMB 1991 and YPMB.mp3, Undated
      - Untitled, Undated; 1 (Box 519)
    - Other
      - Master Teaching Seminars: Marching Bands of America, 1985 Summer; 1 (Box 289)
      - NECBA: Harry Begian at Central Connecticut State University, 1986 March 27; 1 (Box 290)
      - NECBA: Begian rehearsal, 1986 March 27; 1 (Box 291)
      - NECBA: Keith Wilson at Yale, 1987; 1 (Box 292)
      - "Sights and Sounds", Art of STS-26, 1989 September 29; 1 (Box 293)
      - NECBA, 1990; 1 (Box 294)
      - Clinton Inaugural Musical Festivities, 1992; 1 (Box 295)
      - Miller Testimony tape 2, 1994 February-March; 1 (Box 296)
      - Yale Class of 1959 35th Year Reunion, 1994 May 26-29; 1 (Box 297)
      - Yale 1945W, The Fiftieth, by Yale University School of Medicine, 1995; 1 (Box 298)
      - Yale Drumline Show, 1996 December 15; 1 (Box 299)
      - Michigan's Motors, Grand Ledge HS, 1996 May 22; 1 (Box 300)
      - DIT College of Music Concert Band, 1996 September 7; 1 (Box 301)
      - Duffy/Hartt at Litchfield High School, 1999 April 9; 1 (Box 302)
      - Reading session, New England Band Conference, 2000 March 31; 1 (Box 303)
      - A Video Tour of Yale College, Office of Undergraduate Admissions Promo Video, 2001; 1 (Box 304)
      - Some Reflections on Thomas Duffy by Alan Terricciano '83, 2002 April 2; 1 (Box 305)
      - ECAE #2 Hockey, 2009 spring; 1 (Box 520)
      - Bob Reynolds at UNH, Undated; 1 (Box 306)
      - Boston Symphony Orchestra Concert, Undated; 1 (Box 307)
      - New Trier at Glenn Miller Orchestra, Undated; 1 (Box 308)
      - Marv's Mike - "Marches and Metric", Undated; 1 (Box 309)
      - Claiborne's Thingy; My Baby, Claiborne Junior, born 4/27 at 1:45 am, weighing 1/2 a pound, Undated; 1 (Box 310)
      - Glenn Miller - America's Musical Hero (1 hour documentary), Undated (Box 311)
      - D-Day 1944 - Bill Stack interview, Undated; 1 (Box 312)
      - CBDNA reading session, random, Undated; 1 (Box 313)
      - Audition tape, REH.: Holst Japanese Suite III, Master, Undated; 1 (Box 314)
      - Lingenfelter, Undated; 1 (Box 315)
      - Peter Arvantely, Undated; 1 (Box 316)
      - Composer interview, Undated; 1 (Box 317)
      - Ryder, Undated; 1 (Box 521)
      - Seth Kostko '93, Undated; 1 (Box 522)
      - Michael Berman, Duffy video clips, Undated; 1 (Box 523)
      - Stafford, miscellaneous stuff, Undated; 1 (Box 524)
      - Chris Marcil, Undated; 1 (Box 525)
      - AL, Undated; 1 (Box 526)
      - O11.2, Undated; 1 (Box 527)
      - Korean drumming, Undated; 1 (Box 528)
      - Subscribers, Undated; 1 (Box 529)
  - Computer files
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - Yale Concert Band 04-05 Prof. Photo Shoot, 2015-A-0063-0001; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Band 05-06, 2015-A-0063-0002; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Band Parents Weekend and Veteran Concert 06, 2015-A-0063-0003; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Band 07 TIF 20MB JPG 1 MB, 2015-A-0063-0004; 1 (Box 553)
    - Concert Band 08 etc., 2015-A-0063-0005; 1 (Box 553)
    - James R. Anderson Photography-Yale Concert Band Parents Weekend Concert, 2015-A-0063-0006; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Band 11/08, 2015-A-0063-0007; 1 (Box 553)
    - Sights and Sounds of Yale Music 2010, 2015-A-0063-0008; 1 (Box 553)
    - Levin Opus 20 Yale School of Music February 14, 2013, 2015-A-0063-0009; 1 (Box 553)
    - Duffy FCP Raw, 2015-A-0063-0010; 1 (Box 553)
    - Info CD 2006 Yale Concert Brand Yale Jazz Ensemble Yale Precision Marching Mand, 2015-A-0063-0011; 1 (Box 553)
    - Year in Review 2008 43B, 2015-A-0063-0012; 1 (Box 553)
    - Concert for Haiti For Review Only, 2015-A-0063-0013; 1 (Box 553)
    - Yale Concert Band Raw Part 1 "Newsreel Yale Remembers World War II April 8, 1994 Woolsey Hall, 2015-A-0063-0014; 1 (Box 553)